(
"ai_sub_version": "2.8.2",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"ollama_search": (
"key": "**********"
),
"web_search_tool": "ollama",
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Good morning, good afternoon, good evening,
wherever you are in the Realms!
Welcome! You're watching Now That's a Bop on ERB TV!
I'm your host... Ohohohoho!
Roses are red, the fire of my heart is blue,
also known as the Scarlet Queen,
the harbinger of order, leader of Justice!
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
Lovely to see you, to see you... lovely!
We have an excited crowd of Rosarians here! Huzzah!
And a great crew ready to bring some awesome tunes to you all! Huzzah!
We've got a massive lineup of absolute bops and a halfs!
Tonight we have a special theme...
We are celebrating music from the 80s!
Make sure you folks at home, if you're enjoying the show,
please let us know using the hashtag...
#ERBday2026! ERBday 2026!
Right up there! Right up there!
OK! Let's get started with our first bop.
Here we go! It's Friday Chinatown!
フライデイ・チャイナタウン
[Song: Friday Chinatown]
It's So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
It's so fly-day, fly-day Chinatown
真夜中の人ごみに
In the midnight crowd
It's So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
It's so fly-day, fly-day Chinatown
はじけるネオンサイン
The neon signs are popping
肩にぶつかる外人
Foreigners bumping into shoulders
ウインクを投げる
Throwing winks
知らん顔のあなた
You with an indifferent face
とまどいのひとコマ
A moment of bewilderment
踊りつかれていても
Even if I'm tired from dancing
朝まで遊ぶわ
I'll play until morning
港の見える場所で
At a place where I can see the harbor
何か飲みたいのよ
I want to have a drink
It's So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
ジャスミンに接吻を
A kiss for the jasmine
It's So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
私も異国人ね
I, too, am a foreigner
お店にならぶ 絹のドレスを指さす
Pointing at the silk dress lined up in the shop
渋い顔のあなた わがままがいいたい
You with a grim face, I want to act selfish
愛想笑いのおばさん きっと似合うわと
The middle-aged woman with a forced smile says,
"It'll definitely suit you"
どこか静かな場所で 着がえてみたいのよ
I want to try it on somewhere quiet
It's So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
絹ずれの月あかり
The rustling of silk in the moonlight
It's So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
私も異国人ね
I, too, am a foreigner
It's So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
ジャスミンに接吻を
A kiss for the jasmine
It's So Fly-Day Fly-Day CHINA TOWN
私も異国人ね
I, too, am a foreigner
男のコになりたい
[Title: I Want To Be A Boy]
男のコになりたいのよ 私
I want to be a boy, me
星のハイウェイ バイク飛ばし 見え
Flying down the highway of stars on a bike, look
あいつのあとを 透けてゆくのさ
Transparently following the path of that guy
そして夢をききたい
And I want to hear your dreams
今日一日だけでいい
Just for today is enough
リボンをほどいて 男のコにさせておいて
Unfasten the ribbon and let me be a boy
朝まで一緒だけど
Together until morning, but...
Chance いつか Chance 二人 Dance するとき
Chance, someday chance, when we dance together
君は不意に女に戻るの
You suddenly return to being a woman
男のコになりたいような スカート
Like I want to be a boy, this skirt
世界中を自由に旅したい
I want to travel freely around the world
バラを一輪 飾るスーツで
With a suit decorated with a single rose
最後の日を決めるの
Deciding on the final day
今日一日だけでいい
Just for today is enough
すべてをかなえて 女の子は見せない
Fulfilling everything, I won't show the girl
素顔が見たいの
I want to see your true face
Chance いつか Chance 二人 Dance するとき
Chance, someday chance, when we dance together
君はあいつ好みの耳になりそう
You'll likely become the ears he likes
Sweet couple beep beep pu
Beep pop beep beep pu
今日一日だけでいい
Just for today is enough
リボンをほどいて
Untie the ribbon
男の子にさせておいて
Let me act like a boy
朝まで一緒ね
We're together until morning
だけどジャン！
But, BAM!
いつかジャン！
Sometime, BAM!
二人ダン！ するときには
When we both DANCE!
ふいに女に戻るの
I suddenly return to being a girl
Sweet couple beep beep pu
Beep pop beep beep pu
SWEET MEMORIES
Lyrics: 松本隆 Music: 大村雅朗
[Title: SWEET MEMORIES
Lyrics: Takashi Matsumoto Music: Masaaki Omura]
Ooh...
なつかしい 痛みだわ
It's a nostalgic pain
ずっと前に 忘れていた
I forgot it a long time ago
でもあなたを見たとき
But when I saw you
時間だけ 後戻りしたの
Time itself seemed to go backward
「幸福？」と 聞かないで
Don't ask me, "Are you happy?"
嘘つくのは上手じゃない
I'm not very good at lying
友だちならいるけど
I have friends, but...
あんなには燃えあがれなくて
I can't feel that fire again
失った夢だけが
Only the dreams I lost
美しく見えるのは何故かしら
Why do they look so beautiful?
過ぎ去った優しさも
Even the kindness of the past
今は甘い記憶 Sweet memories
Is now a sweet memory, Sweet memories
Don't kiss me baby
We can never be
So don't add more pain
Please don't hurt me again
I have spent so many nights
Thinking of you
Longing for your touch
I have once loved you so much
あの頃は若過ぎて
We were too young back then
悪戯に傷つけあった二人
Two people who hurt each other in vain
色褪せた 哀しみも
Even the faded sadness
今は遠い記憶 Sweet memories
Is now a distant memory, Sweet memories
Ooh...
La la la...
失った夢だけが
Only the dreams I lost
美しく...
Look beautiful...
見えるのはなぜかしら
I wonder why I can see them
過ぎ去った優しさも今は
Even the kindness of the past, now...
甘い記憶
Sweet memories...
Sweet memories
You are watching ERB TV!
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame TELEVISION
[Text: Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame Television]
Brilliant, Sora! That was a masterclass in elegance.
My heart is still melting doki doki!
ありがとう！ Thank you!
Thank you! Thank you!
It was such a sweet time singing with everyone!
I get it, I get it. Sweet time, sweet memories. I see, I see.
And the lovely Nerissa Ravencroft! You look absolutely smashing tonight!
Oh Liz, you're such a flatterer. I was watching from the wings and I couldn't stop humming along.
Oh! I have a question for you guys!
So if you two formed a unit, what would your name be?
Something flashy for the '80s charts!
うーん、そうね...
Hmm, well...
We have something in common, don't we? Blue!
Blue! And...
You're kind of legendary, and I'm a demon... so me too!
How about "BLUE MEGAMISAMA"?
つまり！ BLUE MEGAMISAMA!
In other words... BLUE MEGAMISAMA!
Oh! I like that! I like that a lot! Whoa! BLUE MEGAMISAMA!
Beautiful! So cool!
Sora, here's a question for you.
We all know you are an idol, but tonight you look like a movie star!
Which '80s movie would you want to star in?
Ah... the '80s... E.T.!
E.T.! E.T.! E.T.!
Oh, that's a good one! Yeah, yeah!
I'll get my bike and you can hop in my basket!
Nerissa, question for you!
You've got a powerful voice! What is your favorite powerful band from the '80s?
I don't know if I'd call them powerful... but you know the answer...
Before I even say it, it's The Smiths!
I've monitored you enough that I already knew the answer!
But that's still a great answer! Thank you!
All right! I better get off and get ready for the next wild track!
I'll leave you guys to it! Ta-ra, loves, ta-ra! Bye-bye!
You are watching ERB TV!
All right then, let's move on to the next song, darlings!
One, two... Cobra! Huzzah!
コブラ
[Title: Cobra]
Lyrics: 冬杜花代子 / Music: 大野雄二
[Lyrics: Kayoko Fuyumori / Music: Yuji Ohno]
街をつつむ Midnight fog
Midnight fog surrounding the streets
孤独な Silhouette 動き出せば
A lonely silhouette, once it starts moving
それは まぎれもなく ヤツさ
It's unmistakably him
コブラ Leaving me blue
Cobra, Leaving me blue
コブラ Missing you true
Cobra, Missing you true
コブラ Leaving me blue
Cobra, leaving me blue
コブラ Missing you true
Cobra, missing you true
コブラ Only few memories after you
Cobra, only few memories after you
背中にまといつく翳りは
The shadow clinging to his back,
オトコという名のものがたり
Is a story called a man,
許されるはずもない Peace & Love
There's no forgiveness, just peace & love.
空をよぎる Silent voice
Crossing the sky, a silent voice,
おさえた Violence
Suppressing the violence,
うずくたびにひとり
Every time it aches,
闇を仰ぐ ヤツさ
He looks up at the darkness alone, it's him.
コブラ Leaving me blue
Cobra, leaving me blue,
コブラ Missing you true
Cobra, missing you true,
コブラ Only few memories after you
Cobra, only few memories after you.
ハートに刻まれたあの日は
That day carved into his heart,
ロマンと呼ぶには熱過ぎて
Was too hot to call romance,
めぐりくるはずもない Peace & Love
And there's no way it will come around again, peace & love.
Don't you know?
No, no...
形の見えない繋がりで感じたい
I want to feel a connection that can't be seen
Heart to heart
ときめき確かめ あぶなくじゃ
Confirming the excitement, if it's dangerous...
Don't you know? No, no, it's love!
You are watching...
ERB TV!
えい！
Heave-ho!
んんー！
Nnngh!
せい！
Hah!
恋におちて -Fall in love-
[Title: Fall in Love]
もしも願いが叶うなら
If my wishes could come true,
吐息を白いバラに変えて
I'd change my sighs into white roses,
逢えない日には部屋じゅうに
And on days when we can't meet,
飾りましょう 貴方を想いながら
I'd decorate the whole room, thinking of you.
Darling, I want you 逢いたくて
Darling, I want you, I want to see you so much,
ときめく恋に駆け出しそうなの
I feel like running into this pounding love.
迷子のように立ちすくむ
I stand still like a lost child,
わたしをすぐに届けたくて
Wanting to reach you immediately.
ダイヤル回して 手を止めた
I dialed your number, then stopped.
I'm just a woman ah… Fall in love
If my wishes can be true
Will you change my sighs to roses, whiter roses
Decorate them for you
Thinkin' 'bout you every night and find out where I am
I am not livin' in your heart
Darling, I need you
どうしても口に出せない願いがあるのよ
There's a wish I simply cannot put into words.
土曜の夜と日曜の
Because I always want you on Saturday nights
貴方がつねに欲しいから
and on Sundays too.
ダイヤル回して 手を止めた
I dialed your number, then stopped.
I'm just a woman ah… Fall in love
Darling, you love me 今すぐに
Darling, you love me, right now,
貴方の声が聞きたくなるのよ
I find myself wanting to hear your voice.
両手で頬を押さえても
Even if I hold my cheeks with both hands,
途方に暮れる夜が嫌い
I hate these nights when I'm at a loss.
ダイヤル回して 手を止めた
I dialed your number, then stopped.
I'm just a woman ah… Fall in love
Don't you remember when you were here
Without a thinking we were caught in fire
I've got a love song but where it goes
恋におちて -Fall in love-
[Song: Fall in Love]
Three...
loving hearts are
pulling apart of world...
Can't stop you,
can't hold you,
can't wait no more!
I'm just a woman,
fall in love.
I'm just a woman...
RIDE ON TIME
Lyrics, Music: 山下達郎
[Song: RIDE ON TIME]
[Lyrics, Music: Tatsuro Yamashita]
青い
Running through
水平線を
the blue horizon
いま駆け抜けてく
now
とぎすまされた
Feeling the flow of time,
時の流れ感じて
sharpened and refined
ときめきへと
The world begins to move
動き出す世界は
towards excitement
忘れかけてた
The visit of a distant dream
遠い夢の訪れ
I had almost forgotten
RIDE ON TIME
さまよう想いなら
If you have wandering thoughts
やさしく受け止めて
Receive them gently
そっと包んで
Wrap them up softly
RIDE ON TIME
心に火を点けて
Light a fire in your heart
あふれる喜びに
Spread the overflowing joy
拡がれ RIDE ON TIME
RIDE ON TIME
僕の輝く未来
My shining future,
さあ回り始めて
now begins to revolve
虚ろな日々も全て
Even the hollow days
愛に溶け込む
all melt into love
AH 何という朝
AH What a morning
今すぐ君のもと
I'll go to deliver it to you right now
届けに行こう
I'll go to deliver it
燃える心迷わず
A burning heart, without hesitation
RIDE ON TIME
時よ走り出せ
Time, start running
愛よ光り出せ
Love, start shining
目もくらむ程
So bright it's blinding
RIDE ON TIME
心に火を点けて
Light a fire in your heart
飛び立つ魂に送るよ
I'll send it to the soul that takes flight
RIDE ON TIME
届けに行こう
I'll go to deliver it
燃える心
A burning heart
いまこそ
Right now
RIDE ON TIME
時よ走り出せ
Time, start running
愛よ光り出せ
Love, start shining
目もくらむ程
So bright it's blinding
RIDE ON TIME
心に火を点けて
Light a fire in your heart
飛び立つ魂に送るよ
I'll send it to the soul that takes flight
RIDE ON TIME
さまよう想いなら
If you have wandering thoughts
やさしく受け止めて
Receive them gently
そっと包んで
Wrap them up softly
RIDE ON TIME
Oh ride on time 時よ走り出せ
Oh, ride on time, time, start running
愛よ光り出せ 目も眩むほど
Love, shine so brightly that even the eyes are dazzled
Oh ride on time 心に火をつけて
Oh, ride on time, ignite the fire in the heart
飛び立つ魂に 贈るよ ride on time
Offered to the soaring soul, ride on time
Ride on time 彷徨う想いなら
Ride on time, if wandering feelings
優しく受け止めて そっと包んで
Gently accept and softly embrace
Oh ride on time 心に火をつけて
Oh, ride on time, ignite the fire in the heart
溢れる喜びに 広がれ ride on time
Spread in overflowing joy, ride on time
Ride on time 時よ走り出せ
Ride on time, time, start running
愛よ光り出せ 目も眩むほど
Love, shine so brightly that even the eyes are dazzled
Ride on time 心に火をつけて
Ride on time, ignite the fire in the heart
You're watching Erb TV!
I don't know how to dance...
アンビリーバボー！ここは1980年代の高校のディスコかしら！
Unbelievable! Are we in a 1980s high school disco?
お、ディスコディスコ！いえーいディスコ！いえーい！
Oh, disco, disco! Yay, disco! Yay!
この制服似合ってる？
Does this uniform suit me?
最高にキュートよ！
It's super cute!
二人ともとってもカワイイわ！
You both look kawaii!
でも本当の疑問は、世界がこの魅力に耐えられるかってことよ！
But the real question is, is the world ready for such charm?
見ている人全員の心を奪っちゃったわね。私の心もね！
You've captured the very heart of everyone watching, including mine!
リズ、これってもしかして本物？
Liz, is this mustache real?
ちょっとちょっと！手を離して！
Hey, hey, hey! Hands off!
これは最高級のエグゾーディアンの工芸品なんだから！
This here is top-tier Great Exodian craftsmanship!
でもみんなに"Mustach(口髭)"な質問をさせて！
But I mustache you a question!
(※Must ask(聞かなきゃ)と掛けてます)
(※A pun on "must ask")
ころね！あなたはタフなワンちゃんだって聞いてるわ！
Korone! I heard you're a tough pooch!
あなたとマリンならどっちが学校の番長になるかしら？
Between you and Marine, who would be the leader of the school?
さあ、ころね。かかってこい！
Char, Korone! Come at me!
オーケー、マリン。カモン！
Okay, Marine! Come on!
なんてこった！やめて！やめて！やめて！
What the frig? Break it off! Break it off! Break it off!
レディーズ、ここは80年代よ。
Ladies, this is the 80s.
物事にダンスバトルで解決しましょう！
We settle things with a dance-off!
ダンス？ダンスバトル！
Dance? Dance-off!
それじゃあ次の質問よ！
Which leads me to my next question!
ダンスバトルならどっちが勝つかしら？
Who would win in a dance battle?
さて！もっとお喋りしたいけど、私は行かなくちゃ！
Anyway, anyway... I'd love to stay and chat, but I gotta dash.
ころね、マリン、次の曲を紹介してくれるかしら？
Korone, Marine, please lead us into the next song.
よろしくね！それじゃあね！
Cheers ladies, let's go!
オッケー！
Okay!
次の曲は何かな？
Now, what's our next song?
エネルギッシュな曲と聞いてますよ！
I hear it's an energetic one!
よし、準備はいいみたいだね！
All right, it looks like everything's ready!
オラに元気をわけてくれ！
Lend me your energy!
ハッ！
Huzzah!
Sparking!
光る雲を突き抜け Fly Away (Fly Away)
Piercing through the shining clouds, Fly Away (Fly Away)
からだじゅうに広がるパノラマ
A panorama spreading through my whole body
顔を蹴られた地球が怒って (怒って)
The Earth, kicked in the face, gets angry (angry)
火山を爆発させる
And makes the volcanoes explode
溶けた氷の中に
Inside the melted ice
恐竜がいたら 玉乗り仕込みたいね
If there were dinosaurs, I'd want to train them to balance on balls
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
何が起きても気分は へのへのカッパ
No matter what happens, I'm cool as a cucumber
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
胸がパチパチするほど 騒ぐ元気玉...
My chest is crackling with excitement, a roaring Spirit Bomb...
騒ぐ元気玉…Sparking!
The Genki-Dama roars… Sparking!
空を 急降下 Jet Coaster (Coaster)
Diving through the sky, a rollercoaster (coaster)
落ちてゆくよ パニックの楽園へ
I fall into a Paradise of panic
景色 逆さになると愉快さ (愉快さ)
When the scenery turns upside-down, I’m happy
山さえ お尻に見える
The mountains even look like butts
悩む時間はないよ
There’s no time for worrying
何処かに潜む「ビックリ！」に逢いたいから
’Cause there’s a “surprise!” I want to find
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
頭カラッポの方が 夢詰め込める
An empty head is easier to stuff with dreams
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
笑顔ウルトラZで
With a smile that’s Ultra Z
今日もアイヤイヤイヤイヤイ…
Even today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
何が起きても気分は へのへのカッパ
Whatever happens, it won't bother me one bit
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
胸がパチパチするほど
As loud as my heart pounds
騒ぐ元気玉…Sparking!
The Genki-Dama roars… Sparking!
Sparking!
You are
watching
ERB TV
Absolutely bonkers! Standing ovation!
And round of applause for that spectacular energy.
We did it!
Welcome to the desk, Nene and Iroha!
リズ お誕生日おめでとう！
Liz, happy birthday!
Oh yes, it's my birthday!
Happy birthday to you!
リズ とってもパワフルだね！
Liz, you are powerful!
パワフルなダンスにパワフルな歌唱！
Powerful dance, powerful singing!
そしてパワフルなポーズね！
And powerful pose!
Oh yeah, very powerful poses.
最高にキュート！
So cute!
Cute? Nene, so cute. Liz love.
We're very powerful!
Everyone was so powerful!
みんなブロンドヘアーだね！
Everyone into blond hair!
Yeah, blond hair is super powerful! Super Saiyan!
Super Saiyan blond hair, you know! Very powerful!
The strongest!
I felt everyone's power.
And Nene, your energy is like a dragon!
Show the viewers your most powerful dragon pose?
ドラゴンポーズ！
Dragon pose!
ガオーッ！
Gaoh!
ドラゴンマウス ガッチンガッチン
Dragon mouse, gatchin gatchin
That was incredible!
And Iroha, your focus during that dance was amazing.
Demonstrate your finest samurai warrior stance?
OK 見てて！拙者は侍だよ！
OK look! I'm a samurai!
ジャキーン！
Shakin!
So strong! Strong samurai warrior!
We performed in a big group tonight.
Who was the most 'chala' member at rehearsals?
Are you pointing to Nene?
リハーサル中もずっとそうだったよね
During rehearsal, Nene-senpai was always...
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
みんなでやろう！みんなで、えーっと...
Let's do it together! Let's all, uh...
せーの！ Congratulations Standing Ovation!
Ready... set... Congratulations Standing Ovation!
ねえねえ、ねね先輩が一番チャラいわ！
Hey, Nene-senpai is the most flashy one!
チャラチャラ！
Flashy, flashy!
本当に素晴らしい時間だったね！
That was truly a marvelous time!
でも悲しいことに、次で最後の曲になっちゃうの。
グランドフィナーレの準備をしなくちゃ！
But sadly, the next one is our final song.
I must prepare for the grand finale!
すぐに戻ってくるね！ねね、いろは、
少しの間観客のみんなを楽しませておいてね！
I'll be back very soon! Nene, Iroha,
please keep everyone entertained for a bit!
二人にお願いしたよ！オッケー、待ってろ！また後でね！
I'm counting on you two! Okay, wait for me! See you later!
バイバーイ！頑張って！
Bye-bye! Good luck!
さあ、今夜のスターのリズは一体最後に
何を見せてくれるのでしょうか？
Now, what kind of final performance will tonight's star,
Liz, show us?
楽しみですね！じゃあ皆さん、見るそのままので！
それでは行きましょう！
We are so excited! Everyone, stay tuned!
Here we go!
おい！ You're watching ERB TV!
Hey! You're watching ERB TV!
せーの、万歳！
Ready... set... Huzzah!
POLLYANNA (I BELIEVE IN YOU)
[Song: Pollyanna (I Believe in You)]
I believe the morning sun
Always gonna shine again
And I believe a pot of gold
Waits at every rainbow's end
I believe in roses kissed with dew
Why shouldn't I believe the same in you?
I believe in make-believe
Fairy tales and lucky charms
And I believe in promises
Spoken as you cross your heart
I believe in skies forever blue
Why shouldn't I believe the same in you?
You may say I'm a fool
Feelin' the way that I do
You can call me Pollyanna
Say I'm crazy as a loon
I believe in silver linings
And that's why I believe in you
I believe there'll come a day
Maybe it will be tomorrow
When the bluebird flies away
All we have to do is follow
I believe a dream can still come true
Why shouldn't I believe the same in you?
You may say I'm a fool
Feelin' the way that I do
I believe in friends and laughter
And the wonders love can do
I believe in songs and magic
And that's why I believe in you
You may say I'm a fool
Feelin' this way about you
There's not much I can do
I'm gonna be this way my life through
'Cause I still believe in miracles
I swear I've seen a few
And the time will surely come
When you can see my point of view
I believe in second chances
And that's why I believe in you
ハロー、愛するみんな
Hello, sweethearts!
Lovely to see you, to see you... Lovely!
ERB TVの初放送はどうだった？
What did you think of the first show on ERB TV?
楽しんでくれたかしら？選曲はどう思った？
Did you enjoy it? What did you think of the song choices?
素晴らしいゲストたちと一緒にパフォーマンスできて 私は本当に嬉しかったわ
I really hope you loved it as much as I loved performing with such amazing guests.
Huzzah!
ロザリアンのみんな 準備はいい？
Rosarians, to arms! Are you ready?
サプライズの準備はできててる？
Are you ready for the surprise?
みんなに見せたい素敵なものがあるの
I have something lovely to present to all of you.
いくわよ... 3... 2... 1...
Here we go... 3... 2... 1...
誕生日記念グッズよ！
I have birthday merch!
まずはこちら
First up is this.
この誕生日記念グッズの美しいキービジュアルが タペストリーになったわ！
The beautiful key visual art of this birthday merch is on a tapestry!
ボビーとロザリアンと一緒にリラックスしているところなの
I'm relaxing with Bobby and a cute Rosarian after a dance workout.
この素敵なレトロ風タペストリーを飾って 写真を撮って私に見せてね！
Please display this wonderful retro-style tapestry and take pictures for me to see please!
みんながどんな風にお部屋に飾ってくれるかすごく楽しみだね
Would absolutely love to see how you decorate the room with it.
テレビスタジオに来てくれたんだから 自分専用のERB TVマグカップも手に入れてね
As you've visited the TV studio, make sure to pick up your very own ERB TV mug.
テレビで私を見ながらこれで水分補給してね！
Use it to hydrate while watching me on the telly.
「お母さん私ERB TVに出てるよ！」
Mom, I'm on ERB TV!
「見て テレビに出てるわ！」
Hey Mom, I'm on the telly!
たぶん今頃クイーンマザーもこれを見ているわね
I go saying that and most likely right now Queen Mother is watching this on the telly.
次はみんなも私も欲しがっていたもの...
Next, you've all been wanting this, and so have I...
ロザリアンのぬいぐるみよ！
A Rosarian plushie!
超ハッピー〜
Ah, I'm so freaking happy!
私の冒険は忠実で素晴らしいロザリアンのみんながいなければ成り立たなかった
My adventures have been nothing without my loyal amazing Rosarians.
これであなただけのブラッドフレイム王国の力強いロザリアンを飼えるわね
Now you can have your very own Rosarian Bloodflame Kingdom powerful pooch.
私はあなたの剣 あなたは私の盾 私たちは一緒なら最強！
I am your sword and you are my shield. We are powerful together.
That's right!
次は激アツ ピンバッジ4個セットよ！
Next, we have a set of four pin badges.
私がピンバッジ集めが大好きなのは知っているわよね
Y'all know I love collecting pin badges.
新しいコレクションに加えてね
And here's some new ones for you to collect.
ERB TVロゴ シールド 肉球 そしてBFKヘッドバンドをしたロザリアンよ
We have the ERB TV logo badge, shield badge, Rosarian paw, and a Rosarian with a headband on saying BFK.
レペゼン Blood Flame Kingdom
Bloodflame Kingdom represent!
80年代風のヘッドバンドすごく似合っているわよ
You all look amazing with an 80s headband on, I must say.
最後に英語と日本語の両方で新しいボイスパックを収録したわ
Lastly, I recorded another voice pack in both English and Japanese.
ボイスパックのタイトルは「エリザベスと体操」
The voice pack is called Exercise with Elizabeth.
一緒に運動して私たちの修行に加わってね
So join me on our training arc as we exercise together.
さらなる高みを目指すために...！
Onwards and upwards!
フルセットを購入してくれた方には フルセット購入特典があるわね！
Then if you purchase the whole set, the full shebang, there's a full set purchase bonus.
キービジュアルのポストカードがもらえるんだけどそれだけじゃないの
You get a postcard with the key visual on it, but that's not all.
数量限定版には 私の直筆サイン入りポストカードが入っているわ
The limited quantity includes a postcard with a handwritten signature by yours truly.
限定版がなくなっても 複製サイン入りのポストカードはもらえるからね
Please do not worry, even when those run out, you still get the postcard with my replica signature.
以上が生誕グッズのフルセットでした！
And that is the full set of my birthday merch.
どうだったかしら？
What do you think?
グッズには愛を込めたわ
There's been a lot of love put into this merch.
特にロザリアンを抱っこするのが待ちきれない！
And I especially can't wait to cuddle my own Rosarian plushie!
ライブが終わる前に ゲストのみんなに特別な感謝を伝えたいわ
Wow, before we wrap up, I'd like to give a special thanks to the guests.
みんなと一緒にパフォーマンスできて光栄だったわ
It is an honor performing with you all. I'll treasure these sweet memories forever.
スタッフのみんなも素晴らしい仕事をありがとう
Thank you to the crew, amazing job everyone.
振り付けを教えてくれたダンスの先生たちもありがとう 誇らしい気持ちにさせられたかな
Thank you to my dance teachers who made the choreo. I hope it made you proud with my moving and grooving.
そしてなによりもロザリアンのみんな 最初の誕生日ライブを見てくれてありがとう
Most of all, thank you, my beautiful kingdom, my Rosarians, for checking out my first birthday live.
ERB TVの初放送！
First ERB TV show!
最高の曲ばかりだったわよね？
Those were some bops and a half, right?
美味しいものを食べて 水分補給してしっかり寝るのよ
Okay, make sure to eat good noms, hydrate, get good sleeps,
私たちの王国を素晴らしく強く保ちたいからね
because we want our kingdom to be good and strong.
みんなのことが大好き
I love you all very much.
そして何より私の声がみんなの力になりますように
And most of all, let my voice be your strength.
ByeBye~
Bye bye!
You're watching ERB TV
歌ってみた 3B
[Title: 3B Cover]